SARVANI KASA

kasasarvani@gmail.com / 8886319709,8328685498 / 1911-Manjeera Majestic Homes, JNTUH Road, KPHB, Hyderabad, Telangana

Summary

Hard-working professional with 7+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of confidential correspondence. Intend to build a career with leading organization of Hi-tech environment with committed and dedicated people, which will help me to explore myself fully and realize my potential.

Experience

VCS Associate

Amazon Development Center (India) Pvt Ltd • Hyderabad (WFH) 05/2023 - till date

- Supporting customers, drivers, shippers and delivery service partners to ensure successful deliveries
- Resolving technical tasks related to Amazon's website, Prime services and/or digital devices (Echo/Kindle etc.)
- Gathering intelligence to prevent any potential issues that may impact customer experience and delivery performance.

Digital Marketing Specialist(Part time)

DRIM • Online Platform (WFH)

08/2022 - till date

- Personal blogger Manager
- Direct response influencer marketing on social media

Student Success Specialist

BYJUS • Banagalore, Karnataka (WFH)

09/2022 - 11/2022

- Mentor the students assigned to you throughout their BYJU's journey by ensuring they are engaging with the product and content
- Guide the student throughout their academic journey by directing them to right resources, valuable content, and academic learning
- · Leverage multiple communication channels (call, chat, video) to mentor and engage with students and parents
- · Closely monitor and analyze students' performance dashboard to chart the overall progress of the students
- Leverage the dashboards to share a progress report with students and parents regularly
- Drive student's academic and extra-curricular success and performance through constant motivation and counseling
- · Enable students and parents to engage with and utilize the app to fullest
- · Ensure achievement of daily/ weekly/ monthly targets under the guidance of your managers

D-Proc • Hyderabad, Telangana (WFH)

- Produce & execute email campaigns, including building emails from templates and HTML, copywriting and scheduling.
- Testing campaigns, managing testing calendar, recording results and advise on improvements. Testing includes subject lines, message content, CTAs, customer cohorts, and segments, send time and new features intended to drive performance lift.
- Providing regular campaign performance reports that include opens, clicks, conversions, revenue, unsubscribes, etc.

Online Tutor (Part Time)

FREELANCER • Hyderabad, Telangana (WFH) 11/2019 - 08/2021

- Provide private instruction to individual or small groups of students to improve academic performance, improve occupational skills, or prepare for academic or occupational tests.
- Teach students study skills, note-taking skills, and test-taking strategies.
- · Administer, proctor, or score academic or diagnostic assessments.
- · Assess students' progress throughout tutoring sessions.

Assistant Professor

GRIET • Hyderabad, Telangana 03/2015 - 11/2019

- · Evaluate and grade students' class work, assignments, and papers.
- Prepare and deliver lectures to undergraduate or graduate students on topics related to electronics & communication engineering.
- · Initiate, facilitate, and moderate classroom discussions.
- · Compile, administer, and grade examinations, or assign this work to others.
- Maintain student attendance records, grades, and other required records.

Assistant Professor

MCET • Hyderabad, Telangana 06/2012 - 09/2014

- Evaluate and grade students' class work, assignments, and papers.
- Prepare and deliver lectures to undergraduate or graduate students on topics related to electronics & communication engineering.
- · Initiate, facilitate, and moderate classroom discussions.
- Compile, administer, and grade examinations, or assign this work to others.
- · Maintain student attendance records, grades, and other required records.

- Collaborate with web, multimedia, or art design staffs to create multimedia web sites that conform to brand and company visual format.
- Conduct online marketing initiatives, such as paid ad placement, affiliate programs, sponsorship programs, email promotions, or viral marketing campaigns on social media Web sites.
- Optimize Web site exposure by analysing search engine patterns to direct online placement of keywords or other content.
- Communicate and collaborate with merchants, webmasters, bloggers, or online editors to place sales-oriented hyperlinks in high-traffic locations.

Skills

Digtal Marketing, Python, Scratch Programming, Xilinx, C Language, App Inventor (Android App Development Platform), Processing (Android App Development Platform), Linux / Unix, MS Office-(Excel, PP, Word), SQL

Education

MTECH (VLSI & ES) [75.62 %] MCET (JNTUH Affiliated) • Hyderabad, Telangana 11/2014

BTECH (ECE) [66.85 %] MRITS (JNTUH Affiliated) • Hyderabad, Telangana 05/2010